(Emily:)you'd want to come over?
(Raj:)I'm sorry, I don't think
that's a good idea.
(Emily:)Okay. I'm just...
(crying):
I'm having a really hard time,
(Emily:)but that's not your problem,
that's mine.
I-I won't bother you again,
(Emily:)but please know that you'll
always have a place in my heart.
(Emily:)Bye, Raj.
(Emily:)You're a good guy.
(Raj:)Good-bye, Emily.
(sighs):
That was rough, you guys.
(Penny:)I know, but you did it.
I'm so proud of you.
(Raj:)Well, anyway, I'll leave you
to your girls' night.
(Amy:)Are you sure you don't want
to stay here with us?
(Raj:)No, I kind of feel like
being alone right now.
(Bernadette:)Well, if you change your mind,
we'll be here.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Penny:)Say hi to Emily for us.
(Raj:)Will do.
(Howard:)This contract
looks good to me.